# Jatinkumar Parmar Solution Engineer, Project Manager, Data Analyst

Address: India

Verifications: calyptus.co (Open to see who verified my skills and experience)

#### **Contact Information**

Email: parmarjatin4911@gmail.com Phone Number: 917016681896

 LinkedIn:
 <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jhparmar/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/jhparmar/</a>
 GitHub:
 <a href="https://github.com/parmarjh">https://github.com/parmarjh</a>

 Twitter:
 <a href="https://x.com/parmarjatin4911">https://x.com/parmarjatin4911</a>
 Telegram:</a>
 <a href="https://t.me/funinaiofficiaal">https://t.me/funinaiofficiaal</a>

### **Professional Summary**

Hi, I'm Jatinkumar Parmar, a seasoned professional with over 19 years of experience in the tech industry. My passion lies in the exciting fields of data science, Al, ML, and Generative Al. You can find more about my work and projects on my online profiles: Blog: dev.to/jhparmar Github: github.com/parmarjh Daily.dev: dly.to/G54QKfWl3oT Portfolio: https://jatinmu.vercel.app Website: https://i-shiva-ai.vercel.app Youtube:https://youtube.com/@funinaiofficial

### **Work Experience**

Data science AI/ML Researcher & development, Freelancer Researcher

Mar 2024 - Aug 2024

I Jatin parmar. I have done 18+ years, Data Scientist and Researcher with 6+ Years of Experience of Data Science
technology and Research experience in wide functions including predictive modelling, data preprocessing, feature
engineering, machine learning and deep learning. Currently, I work as Sr.Al ML Solution Genai Ilm (Data Scientist) at
shiv ai Ilp. Helps to Collaborate with IBM and AWS specialists to design and build complex enterprise solutions with the
foundation of Red Hat Open Shift,

Data science Al/ML Own Startup, Shiv ai Ilp & ez Ilm	Jun 2023 - Mar 2024
web_A I/ML Product Development Manager, Karma Lab & Plausibility solutions	Oct 2022 - May 2023
Sr.system engineer, SSM Infotech Solution Pvt. Ltd	Oct 2018 - Jul 2022
Project Manager, Technical Support, IL&FS Education and Technology Service	Sep 2017 - Aug 2018
Guest Faculty, Pmkvy	Jul 2012 - Aug 2017

#### **Education**

mahatma Gandhi univercioty - computer science

2014 - 2017

#### **Skills**

Engineering Management Open source

Data Science Project Management

Technical Writing Python

Leadership Communication

R Software Engineering

**Industry & Domain Knowledge** 

AI & ML Blockchain

Computer Vision Cryptocurrency

Design Generative AI

Government Internet of Things

Machine Learning Metaverse

# **Projects**

data science	aiml project list	Jan 1, 2020 - Now
data science	aiml project list	Jan 1, 2020 - Now
data science	aiml project list	Jan 1, 2020 - Now

## Languages

English (Upper-intermediate) Hindi (Advanced) Gujarati (Advanced)

Find out how I'm verified by Calyptus <u>here</u>
Verified resume powered by <u>Calyptus – Web3's leading talent platform trusted from AAVE to Wintermute</u>